COUNTRY ROADS
3...
2...
1...
Almost heaven,    West Virginia
Blue Ridge Mountains, Shenandoah  River
Life is old there,   older than the trees
Younger than the mountains,   growing like a breeze
Country roads,       take me home
To the place         I   belong
West Virginia, mountain mama
Take   me home,     country  roads
All my memories   gather 'round her
Miner's  lady,   stranger  to blue water
Dark  and  dusty,   painted on the sky
Misty taste of moonshine, teardrop in my eye
Country roads,       take me home
To the place         I   belong
West Virginia, mountain mama
Take   me home,     country  roads
I hear her voice in the morning hour, she calls me
The radio reminds me of my home far away
Driving down the road, I get a feeling
That I should have been home   yesterday,        yesterday
Country roads,       take me home
To the place         I   belong
West Virginia, mountain mama
Take   me home,          country  roads
Country roads,   take me home